<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Projects</title>
    <link>https://questionablehandle.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Projects</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2008–2018, Steve Francia and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 13:13:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://questionablehandle.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kafre Images</title>
      <link>https://questionablehandle.github.io/post/pyramidimages/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 13:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://questionablehandle.github.io/post/pyramidimages/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Faces North Face East Face South Face North Face Width of each stone Height of each stone Size (area) of each stone Vertical offset of each stone from its course Relative width of each stone to its course Relative height of each stone to its course Slant of each stone&#39;s local masonry Slant of each stone Angle of the left edge of each stone Angle of the right edge of each stone Largest angle of each stone Individual casing stones Strings of casing stones Horizontal courses of casing stones Extrapolated pyramid outline Width of each stoneColoured by width relative to the average, red = wider, blue = narrower Height of each stoneColoured by height relative to the average, red = taller, blue = shorter Size (area) of each stoneColoured by size relative to the average, red = bigger, blue = smaller Vertical offset of each stone from its courseColoured by vertical offset, red = stone is above course average, blue = stone is below course average (measured between centroid of casing stone, and centroid of the whole course) Relative width of each stone to its courseColoured by relative width to course, red = wider, blue = narrower Relative height of each stone to its courseColoured by relative height to course, red = taller, blue = shorter Slant of each stone&#39;s local masonryColoured by the angle of the local masonry surrounding the stone, red = clockwise (full red at &amp;gt;=7degrees), blue = anticlockwise (full blue at &amp;gt;=7degrees) Slant of each stoneColoured by the angle of the stone, red = clockwise (full red at &amp;gt;=7degrees), blue = anticlockwise (full blue at &amp;gt;=7degrees) Angle of the left edge of each stoneColoured by angle, red = clockwise (full red at &amp;gt;=15degrees), blue = anticlockwise (full blue at &amp;gt;=15degrees) Angle of the right edge of each stoneColoured by angle, red = clockwise (full red at &amp;gt;=15degrees), blue = anticlockwise (full blue at &amp;gt;=15degrees) Largest angle of each stoneColoured by angle, full red at &amp;gt;=15degrees Individual casing stonesColoured by casing stone Strings of casing stonesColoured by strings of casing stones Horizontal courses of casing stonesColoured by course Extrapolated pyramid outlineWhite lines show the projected pyramid outline.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Khafre Casing Stones</title>
      <link>https://questionablehandle.github.io/post/pyramids/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 13:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://questionablehandle.github.io/post/pyramids/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Introduction Oculi omnium in te sperant, Domine, et tu das illis cibum in tempore, aperis manum tuam, et imples omne animal benedictione. Benedic, Domine, nos et dona tua, quae de tua largitate sumus sumpturi, et concede ut illis salubriter nutriti, tibi debitum obsequium praestare valeamus, per Jesum Christum Dominum nostrum.
Contents Main Observations Overview and Comparison of faces Data and Methodology All Observations Acknowledgements Main Observations Construction Consistency The construction of the casing stones still remaining is, in many ways, much more consistent than we might expect from only the second ever attempt at building such a large structure.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
